classle.net 2014-11-09

# Privacy Policy | Classle

###  Privacy Statement

By using our Web site, you agree to comply with our policies. Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our services.

###  What Information Do We Collect

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site usage information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

###  Registration Information

You will provide us information about yourself that will enable us to verify your email address to access and use information, materials and services available from Classle. This information may also be used to enable us to enhance your Site visit or to follow up with you after your visits.

For example, we request information from you when you:

  * Log-on to certain areas of [Classle](https://www.classle.net/) where you may be prompted to provide us with your Log in Name and Password as a condition to gaining access to certain materials or services.

  * Register or sign-up to use a service.

  * Provide feedback in an online survey.

In each of the instances above, we typically ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, Log in Name and Password, as well as, other similar personal information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. On occasion, we may ask for additional information to enable us to provide you with access to and use of certain information, materials and services.

Wherever Classle collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

###  How we use Information

Classle uses your personal information for specific purposes only. The personal information you provide to us when using the Web site, such as your name, postal, e-mail address or telephone number will be kept confidential and used to support your relationship with Classle. Agents or contractors of Classle who are given access to your personal information will be required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for[ Classle ](https://www.classle.net/)

###  Sharing Information with Third Parties

Circumstances may arise where we are required to disclose your personal information to third parties for purposes other than to support your customer relationship with [Classle](https://www.classle.net/), such as in connection with a corporate divestiture or dissolution where we sell all or a portion of our business or assets (including our associated customer lists containing your personal information), or if disclosure is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings.

###  Cookie

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

Use of cookies makes web surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your Passwords, your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular Web site and to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Site will not function properly. You may note additionally that if you visit Classle Web site where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

###  Certain Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties.

###  What about other web sites link in our web site

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

###  Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children below the age of 15. If we learn that we have personal information on a child below the age of 15, we will delete that information from our systems. Even for personal information of children of the age of 15 years and above, the personal information is collected only for the purpose of their educational requirement and service needs as provided by this Web site.

###  Consequences of Violation:

When Classle becomes aware of an alleged violation of its Acceptable Use Policy, Classle will initiate an investigation. During the investigation Classle may restrict Customer 's access in order to prevent further possible unauthorised activity. Depending on the severity of the violation, Classle may, at its sole discretion, restrict, suspend, or terminate Customer's account and pursue other civil remedies. If such violation is a criminal offence, Classle will notify the appropriate law enforcement department of such violation.

###  Your Consent 

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

###  How to contact us

If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, Please contact us at : [info@classle.co.in](mailto:info@classle.co.in)

###  Revisions to This Policy:

Classle reserves the right to revise, amend or modify this policy at any time and in any manner it pleases. Any change or revision will be posted on our Web site.
